{
	"ecosistema":{
			      "momentoDeVida":"habitat",
			      "idMomentoDeVida":5,
			      "servicio":"inversion",
			      "idServicio": 1
				 },


   "datosPersonales":{
  	
  					  "tipoIdentificacion": "CEDULA",
					  "numeroIdentificacion": "10",
					  "nombres": "Usuario 1",
					  "apellidos": "Testeado Primero",
        			  "genero": "Masculino",
					  "ocupacion":{
								    "tipoOcupacion": ["Trabajar", "Estudiar"],
								    "idPais":57,
								    "idDepartamento": 1,
								    "idCiudad": 1,
								    "idBarrio": 10,
								    "coordenadasTrabajo": [{"latitud":6.287564996179178,"longitud":-75.541417192529254}],
								    "coordenadasEstudio": [{"latitud":9.123453456779178,"longitud":-63.987654321529254}]
								   },
        			  "ingresosFinancieros" : 12345,
    				  "capacidadEndeudamiento" : 2345,
    				  "edad": 18,
					  "fechaNacimiento": {
					    "dia": 15,
					    "mes": 8,
					    "anyo": 2000
										}
					},
					
	"preguntasHabitar" : {
								"compartirCon": [{							 
												  "relacion": "Padres",
												  "cantidad": 10
												 }],
																				  
							    "compartirGastos": "si",
							    "cantidadCompartirGastos": 1,
							    "modoTransporte": [{"transporte":"Publico","idTransporte": 1}],
							    "preguntas": [
										    {
										       "idPregunta": "1",
										       "respuestasRq": [
										        {
										          "idRespuesta": "3",
										          "valor": "1"
										        }
										      ]
										    },
										    {
										      "idPregunta": "2",
										      "respuestasRq": [
										        {
										          "idRespuesta": "5",
										          "valor": "1"
										        }
										      ]
										    },
										    {
										      "idPregunta": "3",
										      "respuestasRq": [
										        {
										          "idRespuesta": "8",
										          "valor": "1"
										        }
										      ]
										    },
										    {
										      "idPregunta": "4",
										      "respuestasRq": [
										        {
										          "idRespuesta": "11",
										          "valor": "1"
										        }
										      ]
										    },
										    {
										      "idPregunta": "5",
										      "respuestasRq": [
										        {
										          "idRespuesta": "14",
										          "valor": "1"
										        }
										      ]
										    },
										    {
										      "idPregunta": "6",
										      "respuestasRq": [
										        {
										          "idRespuesta": "20",

										        "valor": 1
										        }
										      ]
										    }]
								
							  },


	"preguntasInvertir" : {
							"inversionMinima":60000000,
							"inversionMaxima":2000000000,
							"invertirDesde": 60000000,
	                         "invertirHasta": 1000000000, 
							    "preguntas": [
											    {
											       "idPregunta": "7",
											       "respuestasRq": [
											        {
											          "elegirZona": 1,
											          "valor" : "1",
											    	  "zona" : [{
										          			   "totalZonas" : 3,
													           "zona1" :{
													          			"nombreDepartamento":"uno",
													          			"idDepartamento":1,
													          			"nombreCiudad":"uno",
													          			"idCiudad":2,
													          			"nombreBarrio":"uno",
													          			"idBarrio":3
													        			},
													        	"zona2" :{
													          			"nombreDepartamento":"dos",
													          			"idDepartamento":4,
													          			"nombreCiudad":"dos",
													          			"idCiudad":5,
													          			"nombreBarrio":"dos",
													          			"idBarrio":6
													        			},	
													          "zona3" :{
													          			"nombreDepartamento":"tres",
													          			"idDepartamento":7,
													          			"nombreCiudad":"tres",
													          			"idCiudad":8,
													          			"nombreBarrio":"tres",
													          			"idBarrio":9
													        			}
										        			}]
											        }
											    				 ]
											    },
											    {
											      "idPregunta": "8",
											      "respuestasRq": [
											        {
											          "idRespuesta": "5",
											          "valor": "1"
											        }
											      ]
											    },
											    {
											      "idPregunta": "9",
											      "respuestasRq": [
											        {
											          "idRespuesta": "23",
											          "valor": "1"
											        }
											      ]
											    },
											    {
											      "idPregunta": "10",
											      "respuestasRq": [
											        {
											          "idRespuesta": ["26","27","28","29","30"],
											          
											          "valor": "1"
											        }
											      ]
											    }
											    
										    ]
								
							}
										    
}